[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the character portrayed by Nick Nolte in the hit movie 48 Hrs.?", "correct_answer": "Jack Cates", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Bates", "Jack Tors", "Jack Lynsmith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first US President with no middle name?", "correct_answer": "George Washington", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Jefferson", "John Adams", "Jimmy Carter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what famous landmark does James Bond kill the villain in A View to a Kill?", "correct_answer": "The San Francisco Golden Gate Bridge", "incorrect_answers": ["The Statue of Christ in Rio de Janeiro", "The Pyramid of Cheops in Egypt", "The Acropolis in Greece"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "123facts.com is a great site, isnt it? But do you know what the .com part stands for?", "correct_answer": "Commercial", "incorrect_answers": ["Competition", "Composition", "Communication"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Taking all thirteen tricks in a game of bridge is referred to as what?", "correct_answer": "Grand slam", "incorrect_answers": ["Small slam", "Knock", "Double nil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Butterflies need the warmth of the sun in order to fly. They cannot possibly fly if the temperature is below this.", "correct_answer": "50 F (10 C)", "incorrect_answers": ["60 F (16 C)", "80 F (27 C)", "70 F (21 C)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were C-3POs last words in Revenge of the Sith?", "correct_answer": "Oh no!", "incorrect_answers": ["The maker has returned!", "Yes, Your Highness.", "Oh, dear."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does a jellyfish have a brain?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Giant Pandas eat oranges and bananas.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the alter ego of Iron Man?", "correct_answer": "Tony Stark", "incorrect_answers": ["Matt Murdock", "Hank Williams", "John Johnson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what movie did Robert De Niro deliver the famous line You talkin to me??", "correct_answer": "Taxi Driver", "incorrect_answers": ["The Godfather, Part II", "The Deer Hunter", "Raging Bull"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What star of Oceans Eleven, Oceans Twelve and Oceans Thirteen starred as detective Graham Waters in the 2004 movie Crash?", "correct_answer": "Don Cheadle", "incorrect_answers": ["George Clooney", "Brad  Pitt", "Matt Damon"]}]